<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CablePlus</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">LoginActivity</string>
    <string name="blank">""</string>
    <string name="thank_you">One of our team member will get in touch with you shortly to get the required booking information.</string>
    <string name="messagebox">special shipping instructions ie: Residential?  Lift Gate Truck needed?  Call Ahead Required? If so, please provide Call ahead phone #.  </string>
    <string name="aboutus">Landscape lighting demands high quality long lasting wiring solutions.
        From simple to complex landscape lighting designs you need high quality low voltage direct burial landscape lighting cable.\n
        Genuine SuperFlex Brand Cable is manufactured to meet the requirements of the ASTM specifications B-3 and B-8.
        SuperFlex wire is soft drawn bare copper with high quality ployvinylchloride insulation.
        for system applications of up to 150 volts and conductor temperatures up to 60 C.\n\n
        Super Flex EZ Pull Boxes provide easy installation.
        Genuine SuperFlex Brand Cable has been supplying the landscaping industry for over 27 years manufactured in the USA
        and distributed across the country and Canada.\n
        Genuine SuperFlex Brand Cable wire is manufactured to such rigid standards that we are able to guarantee zero defects.
        No other wire offers a better guarantee.
        Contact us today for more information about our product line to start your next project
        with the best low voltage direct burial landscape lighting cable in the industry….
        Genuine SuperFlex Brand Cable the Industries Most Trusted Landscape Lighting Cable…  PERIOD</string>


    <string-array name="listArray">
        <item>Headings</item>
        <item>Headings and Details</item>
        <item>All Data</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
